My first time back home in a year!
Father, Mother.
I've completed my year of bridal
training and returned home.
Welcome home, Tiara.
I'm so happy to be home, Mother!
You'll have to tell us all
about Marinforest.
Of course!
I want to hear about all that's
happened here in the past year, too.
I brought some delicious wine.
Shall we all enjoy it together?
Thank you very much, Prince Aquasteed.
P-Pardon me, sir,
but visitors have arrived.
Visitors? But I wasn't expecting anyone.
Well...
It's Prince Hartknights and Lady Akari.
What are those two doing here?
The Villainess Is Adored
by the Prince of the Neighbor Kingdom
Blessings on the Teary Bride
Send them away at once!
Father, I want to speak with Lady Akari.
Tiara...
What are you thinking, Lady Tiararose?!
I can't blame them all for being angry.
If you lose to the sequel's heroine,
I'll never forgive you!
Just Lady Akari alone will do.
But...
Please, Father.
I wish I knew who you got
your stubbornness from.
I will allow it,
but only under the condition that
Prince Aquasteed accompanies you.
Well, then, shall we?
I'm sorry for being so demanding.
Not at all.
I love listening to your demands.
Oh, Lady Tiara! Long time no see!
Oh, and Prince Aqua is here as well.
It's nice to see you again.
I'm so glad you seem well.
Yes, it's been a long time.
It's nice to see you again.
I'm happy to see you're
doing well, Lady Akari.
Yes! I'm working hard
with Prince Hartknights!
Since we're long past the ending,
I feel like I'm playing the next new game!
Sh-She hasn't changed, I see...
Oops! How silly of me!
Lady Tiara, Prince Aqua, allow me
to congratulate you on your marriage.
Thank you, Lady Akari.
Thank you.
I can see it.
Well done winning out
over the sequel's heroine!
I can just tell she's thinking that!
Have you had any trouble this past year?
You weren't bullied, were you?
By the sea fairies, especially!
Well, they don't like me.
Right?! I knew that was
how it would turn out!
That's why I brought these
as your wedding gifts!
Earrings?
Yes!
You've only ever had
the clasping kind before, right?
So I made these!
They're protective charms
that I added the Holy Prayer to!
These are protective charms?
One is the pink color of my hair,
and the other is the dark
blue of Prince Aqua's hair.
If you're going to wear something,
it should be the color
of the one you love!
That's why I wear this!
Yellow is...
Although things are still
a bit awkward between us...
But Prince Hartknights
has been so adorable lately!
He came along with me,
saying he wanted to see you!
Thank you, Lady Akari.
You're welcome!
Since I've received this gift,
I'd like to put them on.
If you want to put them on, I don't mind.
I'm more surprised to see you
being so friendly with Lady Akari.
Y-You have a point.
She did attack me, after all.
But now we're basically partners
in taking down the sequel's heroine!
Heroine?
Tiara?
I-I'm sorry.
But you were there to save me
when that happened, after all.
Honestly... You'd better
tell me the truth one day.
Prince Aqua...
It's clear to me
that you've been holding on to
something you can't tell me.
But...
if you keep me in the dark for too long,
be prepared for the consequences.
It's fine to be all flirty, but do it
when I'm not around, please.
I'm so sorry!
Oh, it's all right.
Just make sure you find happiness!
Thank you.
Father, Mother, I am truly happy.
Tiara...
My father raised me strictly,
and my mother helped me
experience many things.
And all of that gives me strength now.
Yes. We're so glad to see you this happy.
The next time we meet will be
at your wedding in Marinforest.
I'm so excited to see you
in your bridal attire.
Yes!
Tomorrow's the day I finally
become Prince Aqua's wife.
You look beautiful, Lady Tiararose.
I'm so glad you've safely arrived at your
wedding day with Prince Aquasteed!
Oh, really now, Philine.
What's the use in crying now?
The wedding is tomorrow.
You're right. I'm just so excited,
I couldn't help it.
Who could that be?
We weren't expecting anyone, were we?
No. I'll go see.
I'm not going to get a visit
from Lady Icilla, the heroine,
the day before my wedding, am I?
It's Lady Icilla.
I'm sorry to visit when you're so busy.
Not at all. I'm very happy
you came to see me.
Congratulations on your wedding.
I just had to tell you that.
Thank you.
She didn't come to stop the wedding?
I expected her to be in love
with Prince Aqua, but...
Did you, perhaps, think that I had
feelings for Prince Aquasteed?
I don't understand love very well.
I've always believed that my father
would find me a good man to marry.
She doesn't understand love?
Could that be because I exist?
Originally, Lady Icilla was supposed to
nurture her love with Prince Aqua,
one of the conquerable routes.
If not for me, they should
have ended up together.
It wouldn't be right
to apologize now, but...
Lady Icilla, I...
Stop right there.
Lady Akari?!
Once again, congratulations
on your marriage!
It's a pleasure to meet you, Lady Icilla.
My name is Akari.
Thank you for greeting me, Lady Akari.
My name is Icilla Pearllant.
The sequel's heroine...
Yep, just like in the game.
You should be happier.
You got to be the heroine, after all.
Huh?
Lady Akari, please
don't be rude to Lady Icilla!
Oh! I'm sorry!
Did I upset you? I apologize.
N-No, it didn't bother me at all.
Lady Akari, why are you here?
I wanted to see the lucky girl
who got to be the sequel's heroine.
I mean, life ought to be enjoyed!
Icilla's the heroine,
but she's not enjoying it at all!
I suppose this is better than losing
Prince Aqua to her, though.
You really do love otome games, don't you?
You two seem to be very good friends.
Huh?
Yeah! That's exactly right!
I'm Lady Tiara's friend!
That's why I'm so worried about her!
Worried?
Yes! Because you're always
hanging around Prince Aqua!
You'd better not get too close
to my friend's husband!
Lady Akari, what are you...
I'm so sorry, Lady Tiararose.
It's true. I should have been
more considerate.
Please don't say that, Lady Icilla.
You don't need to worry
about that at all.
And Lady Akari,
stop saying things like that!
Sorry.
Excuse me, Lady Tiararose.
Prince Aquasteed will be arriving soon.
Oh, right.
I'm sorry for staying so long.
I'll take my leave now.
A dark blue ribbon...
As expected of the sequel's heroine.
She's such a sweet girl.
Lady Akari, did you come here
to say something to Lady Icilla?
Not really. I only came to see
how the sequel ends.
How it ends? What do you mean by that?
Well, bye!
Lady Akari?!
The Villainess Is Adored
by the Prince of the Neighbor Kingdom
You'd better not get too close
to my friend's husband!
I never meant to do that.
I don't have any romantic feelings
for Prince Aquasteed at all.
His Highness is so brilliant and mature.
He's completely out of my reach...
You're sure I don't look strange?
You're the most beautiful thing
in the world! Be more confident!
Thank you!
Not really. I only came to see
how the sequel ends.
Did she mean some kind of event
is going to happen during the wedding?
This is an otome game world, after all.
There's no way nothing's
going to happen at a wedding.
It's time for you to make your entrance.
Why... does my heart hurt so much?
It's not as if I was in love
with Prince Aquasteed, so why...
Did I actually love him after all?
Was this feeling I had for him
more than just respect?
Prince Aquasteed!
I won't let you do it.
What was I...
Lady Icilla, you really do love
Prince Aquasteed, don't you?
No... I...
I would never...
But... are you telling me
this pain in my chest... is love?
Yeah, I figured this event would happen.
The sequel game has an event where the
romantic interest marries someone else,
but the heroine can intervene and stop it.
The unlock condition
is wearing a ribbon in your love
interest's color to the wedding.
Frankly, I love those
"intervening in the wedding" events.
They get your heart racing, you know?
Because the groom
chooses you over his bride.
But more than that,
I can't allow anyone to ruin my friend's
wedding when she's smiling so happily.
What a coincidence. I agree with you.
Keith, the Forest Fairy King?!
Icilla, was it?
If you try to do anything
to those two, I won't let it slide.
I-I would never do such a thing!
I will do as you wish, Fairy King.
I guess I really can't be by
Prince Aquasteed's side, can I?
I hear someone crying.
I was right. Lady Icilla
really did love Prince Aqua.
N-No!
I've been so scared about whether
this wedding would actually happen.
I kept asking what I'd do if Prince Aqua
chose Lady Icilla at the last moment.
But even if I am standing in the way
of what should be their true love...
Still, I...
Prince Aqua!
Aqua!
Losing isn't an option!
I love Prince Aqua more than anyone!
I want to be with him forever!
Tiara...
I see I've made you feel uneasy again.
P-Prince Aqua...
Prince Aquasteed?
Thank you for attending
our wedding today.
Not at all. Congratulations,
Prince Aquasteed... Lady Tiararose.
Tiararose is the one most precious to me.
I'm sorry, Lady Icilla.
Not at all.
I did admire you, Prince Aquasteed.
But I've moved past it now.
Please go on to be happier
than anyone in the world.
And thank you for teaching me
what love feels like.
Oh, honestly...
You're so cute when you cry,
I just want to eat you up.
Oh, you stopped.
Tiara, this ring is filled with my magic.
Will you accept it?
Of course, Prince Aqua.
And now, I will hold on to you forever.
I will hold on to you forever, too.
Please do.
Tiara...
I love you.
I'll treasure you for life
and make you happy.
Yes. I love you, too.
It looks like stars raining down...
To the next king and his queen!
You have my blessing
for your health and happiness,
and for peace in this kingdom!
Keith!
Fairy King!
The Forest Fairy King
blessed them! Amazing!
What a joyous occasion!
Lady Tiararose! Prince Aquasteed!
Congratulations!
Blast it all. Tiara looks so lovely
when she commands the flowers.
It's troubling how much
it makes me want her.
You'll make Prince Aqua
angry talking like that.
Are you crying again, Tiara?
Oh, goodness. Silly me.
I'm just so happy and blessed,
my tears won't stop flowing.
I'm happy, too.
And now the game is over.
From this point on,
I'll truly live in reality.
No more living at the mercy of a game.
Love is worthless.
A Love Like Ripples on the Water
My love will never be realized.
I need to sink it
into the depths of the sea.
But... when I see him smile, I...